export const questions2 = [
  {
    question: 'What rocket was used to launch the first satellite, Sputnik 1?',
    options: ['RN R-7', 'RN Topol', 'Saturn I', 'Falcon 1'],
    correctAnswer: 'RN R-7',
  },
  {
    question:
      'Which rocket became the main vehicle for the American space missions in the Apollo program?',
    options: ['Saturn V', 'Ares I', 'Atlas V', 'Shuttle'],
    correctAnswer: 'Saturn V',
  },
  {
    question:
      'Which of the following rockets is part of the Space Launch System (SLS) program?',
    options: ['Falcon Heavy', 'Ares V', 'Saturn V', 'SLS Block 1'],
    correctAnswer: 'SLS Block 1',
  },
  {
    question: 'What rocket was designed to launch space missions to Mars?',
    options: ['Falcon 9', 'Changzheng-5', 'Atlas V', 'SpaceX Starship'],
    correctAnswer: 'SpaceX Starship',
  },
  {
    question: 'Which rocket is the most powerful that ever existed?',
    options: ['Saturn V', 'Falcon Heavy', 'New Generation', 'PH Proton'],
    correctAnswer: 'Saturn V',
  },
  {
    question:
      'What rocket was used to deliver the first astronauts to the ISS?',
    options: ['TM Union', 'Shuttle Atlantis', 'Falcon 9', 'Changzhen-2'],
    correctAnswer: 'TM Union',
  },
  {
    question:
      'What is the name of the rocket used to launch missions to the moon as part of the Artemis program?',
    options: [
      'Saturn V',
      'SpaceX Falcon Heavy',
      'Space Launch System (SLS)',
      'PH Proton',
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'Space Launch System (SLS)',
  },
  {
    question:
      'Which rocket was developed for military purposes, but was later used in space programs?',
    options: ['Poplar', 'RN R-7', 'Delta IV', 'Ares I'],
    correctAnswer: 'RN R-7',
  },
  {
    question:
      'Which rocket was the first to successfully launch the space shuttle?',
    options: ['Saturn V', 'Atlas V', 'Shuttle Columbia', 'Falcon 9'],
    correctAnswer: 'Shuttle Columbia',
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which of the following rockets is part of China's program to launch rover missions?",
    options: ['Changzheng-4', 'Changzheng-5', 'Changzheng-6', 'Changzheng-7'],
    correctAnswer: 'Changzheng-5',
  },
];
